Will you marry me?
You knew he was gonna say no!
Well, Billy, I hope you're happy now!
Karma's a bitch, you know.
And it's coming for you.
[JUDE] Who are you?
My name is Jordan. I'm your grandson.
- Thief!
- Okay, fine!
- [JORDAN] Please, calm down.
- I'm leaving.
- T…
[JORDAN] You could've at least
given me a heads-up.
[BILLY] It was wrong, okay? It was wrong.
[JORDAN] Tomorrow is…
[BILLY] It's the death anniversary
of our mothers.
[JORDAN] As long as I'm alive,
I won't stop
until there's justice for you, Mom.
[BILLY] Why are you painting a bird?
[ABI] Because I want to be free.
From taking care of my sick mother.
My father left us.
[BILLY] By the way, I'm Billy.
[ABI] I'm a huge fan of LoveList.
- That's why I know so much about you.
- [BILLY] Thank you.
I'm Abi.
Abi Mercado.
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARIELA] 'Bi!
Is that you?
Come here already! I want to take a bath!
I'm so itchy!
Why'd you get home so late?
- Come on!
- Uh, I'm coming!
Yes, Ma. I'll just change,
then I'll head downstairs.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Val?
I know you're here.
[KNOCKING]
[JORDAN] Val?
Val, can we talk, please?
[MOUTHS] Tell him I'm not here.
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
Oh, sorry. Ma'am Valerie isn't home.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
["KULIMLIM" BY ANGELA KEN PLAYING]
["KULIMLIM" CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
For the utilities.
Mmm. Auntie Pres…
- I've got it.
- [PRECIOUS GIGGLES]
Our electric bill's pretty low this month.
- Mm-hmm?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm supposed to be the mom, right?
- There are two moms here.
- [PRECIOUS GIGGLING]
Go on, just keep it.
I've got something to show you.
It's been two years
since you started paying for our house.
- Eight years! Whoo!
- Eight years to go!
What's eight years? We can do it!
- You can do it!
- [BILLY GIGGLES]
- We can!
[SIGHS HAPPILY]
You know what, Auntie Pres?
Those are the things our dad
promised us back then.
A house of our own.
Helping me finish school.
And every promise he made,
we're the ones fulfilling them
for ourselves now.
Do you really have no plans
to tell your brother
that your father's still alive?
No. He's been dead to us for a long time,
and he's never coming back.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
He's not worth wasting time on anymore.
What I want to focus on
- is LoveList's expansion.
- [GASPS]
We've already ordered the equipment.
And we're about to start hiring again.
[BOTH SQUEALING]
Wait.
What happened to that investor
you were talking about?
I remember you said
your presentation's later, right?
Mm-hmm. It's later!
And yeah! We really have to
close that deal, Auntie Pres.
We really do.
So, let's see.
- Pray for us!
- It's as good as done!
Congrats in advance!
- Not yet!
- I'm so proud of you.
- Thank you.
- That's great!
Not yet!
In a nutshell,
LoveLine is our in-app dating coach
and support feature.
Because, to be honest,
even if you find
your perfect match on LoveList,
relationships can still get messy.
And with this feature,
we will be dealing with
issues of ghosting,
heartbreak, misunderstandings,
and cheating.
So it's like a hotline?
Yes. Yes, exactly.
That's correct.
With LoveLine, users who call
will receive real-time advice
and emotional support
from real people, not bots.
And from not just anyone.
You're getting advice from
licensed psychologists.
Like Billy.
Impressive.
What if someone wants to stay anonymous?
Won't their identity be leaked?
No.
All interactions on LoveLine
are encrypted.
Even the support agents,
they can't see
any of your private information
unless you want them to.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- We love it.
- Oh, thank you.
- Great.
- [WOMAN] However…
As you know, we're not
the final decision-makers.
We still need one more approval.
Of course. Mr. Salcedo, right?
Is he coming?
Oh, no. Actually, he resigned.
We have a new VP.
And as it happens, he's here today.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, Jordan,
I'd like you to meet Mr. Alvin Ramirez.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You've really got some nerve.
[MUSIC STOPS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [BILLY GRUNTS]
- [JORDAN] Hit him!
- [KICK LANDS]
- [ALVIN GROANS]
- [JORDAN] More!
What are you doing here?!
- [JORDAN] Hit him!
- Aren't you happy already?!
Isn't that enough for you?!
- What do you want from me?!
- [JORDAN] Get him!
[MUSIC STOPS]
Alvin?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, Billy.
Hi, Jordan.
What do you mean, "Hi"?!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
AnCore Ventures has actually been
one of our target investors.
You guys invest in digital
and consumer startups, right?
I was able to meet
with Mr. Salcedo last week,
and it turns out you're the one
who took over.
Yeah.
I guess it was a blessing in disguise.
So, Billy, had you known,
would you still have done
the presentation?
Ah, so you knew
this was Billy's all along?
Billy, don't believe anything
he's about to say--
Look.
Jordan. Billy.
I'm not doing this to make it up to you.
[SNICKERS]
I'm just doing my job.
Because I believe in you guys.
In what you guys do
and what you're about to do.
I just know it. I feel it.
It'll be a game-changer.
And I want our company to be part of it.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Then we have a deal.
Dude!
A-Are you serious?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you for your trust, Mr. Ramirez.
Yeah… "trust."
Go ahead. Come on, scold me.
You've been sitting there all quiet.
Cat got your tongue?
He left you at the altar.
He ran away with his pregnant mistress.
Like, do we really have to do this, dude?
Is LoveList in trouble?
- What--
- Oops, no. Excuse me.
LoveList is stable.
It's actually still growing.
That's why we need their investment.
For the expansion.
I thought cheaters were
the one thing you hated most.
And now you're willing
to accept money from one?
Okay, hear me out.
What if you look at it
from a different perspective?
Think of it this way.
We're using Alvin too.
Hmm? Right?
It's just business.
You can't be too emotional about it, dude.
We won't get anywhere if you are.
Maybe you're still in love with him.
[COUGHS] What?!
He might get the wrong idea
and then ask for a second chance.
Come on, Jordan.
I don't care what he thinks.
The goal is to help more women,
not just here in the Philippines,
but all over the world.
Let's go global.
You've got some big ambitions, dude.
Yes! And we're going to make it happen.
Once LoveList becomes successful,
even Oliver will benefit from it.
You know I'd do anything for him, right?
We've lived in a waiting shed
before, remember?
And think about the women
at Angels of Grace.
They'll all benefit
from LoveList's success.
So you think I'd just take
that away from them?
I don't care about Alvin.
But I do care about LoveList
and everyone whose lives
are connected to it.
I can't beat you anyway.
And this area will be used
for the operations of
LoveList's new feature,
which is LoveLine.
Really impressive, Billy.
Thank you.
What made you decide
to create this kind of app?
I think you already know by now
that LoveList isn't just for women
- who are looking for true love.
- Mm-hmm.
It's also for people who've been hurt
and are still hurting.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Yes!
Of course, it's to help people
avoid all the pain,
heartbreak, and emotional scars
caused by cheating men
- who leave women hanging.
- Hmm.
You see, Mr. Ramirez,
these two are incredibly passionate
- about the company.
- [BOTH CHUCKLING]
- [TONI] Of course we are!
- Sure.
We were at that wedding that
never happened. Right?
So yeah, we're passionate.
Blaire?
Blaire, could you please assist
Mr. Ramirez to the café?
- I'll meet you there.
- Uh, no, no, no. It's okay.
I can manage. It's just nearby.
Okay. Thank you.
[TONI CHUCKLES] Take care.
The coffee there is really strong.
Calm down.
Sorry, Billy.
We just can't forget what happened.
What he did.
Charm?
Toni?
I'm grateful for everything
you did to help me back then.
But I need that same support again
for the decision I'm making now.
We need this.
Deal.
Deal. Mm?
Thank you, everyone who believes
in what LoveList stands for.
We are looking forward to
even more success
with this collaboration.
So, big things are ahead for LoveList.
[APPLAUDING]
Billy, thank you.
Thank you, Alvin.
[MAN] Photo op.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow, if I were our chief,
I'd never forgive him.
He'd be canceled in my book.
That's how fearless Billy is.
When she has to face something,
she faces it head-on.
Just look how far she's come.
She's incredibly strong.
I've always looked up to her.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MULTIPLE PHONES CHIMING]
- [MUSIC TURNS UNSETTLING]
- [PHONES KEEP CHIMING]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Look at this.
[INDISTINCT MURMURING]
Alvin! You better stop signing that.
- Gia?
- Let's go!
- What's going on?
What's happening?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GIA GRUNTS]
Explain this!
- NOW THE GUY'S HER BUSINESS PARTNER?
- STRAIGHT OUT OF A SOAP OPERA!
Billy…
I understand we hurt you before,
but that was a long time ago!
We've been keeping to ourselves.
We have kids now.
- Gia.
- Why would you do this now?
How dare you?! Let's go!
Let's go!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [JORDAN] Don't let them leave!
- [PRESS] Ms. Billy!
- [PRESS CLAMORING]
- [WOMAN] What's going on?
[TONI] Okay! Okay!
- Please, calm down.
- You don't need to know.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boom, karma.
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Alvin, wait! Gia!
I never posted that video even back then!
So why did you repost it now?
- Billy.
- What?!
[GIA] You see?
It's reposted on your account.
I didn't do that.
[BILLY] Obviously, it was
hacked! That's not me.
You know, Billy,
trying to reconnect
with you was a mistake.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Deal is off.
[GIA] Let's go.
Alvin, wait. Let's talk about this.
- Let's go.
- Hey, be our convoy, okay?
It's not…
- [CAR ENGINE STARTS]
- It's okay.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BROODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Billy.
Billy, take a look at the comments.
[TONI] Almost all of them are positive.
The netizens are in your favor.
[CHARM] But that's not the point.
The point is that someone
hacked Billy's account
and sabotaged our deal with Alvin,
which is a big blow
to LoveList's expansion.
[JORDAN] Guys.
You have to see this.
[BROODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
There's a lot of comments
being posted in LoveSpeak.
[JORDAN] They're throwing hate on us.
We must have been hacked.
THIS APP IS SO USELESS!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
LET'S STOP USING THIS APP!
The accounts don't have
profile pictures or identification.
Those accounts are not verified,
which means they're not our members.
OMG, we're being attacked by trolls!
What if we lose members because of this?
[JORDAN] Okay! It's okay now.
I've shut down their access point.
I also blocked their IP address.
But, Billy, we're still not safe.
He can reroute
through a different access point
and hit us again.
Not until we find this hacker.
Who would even do this?
I mean, who would hack into our system
and hack into your account?
[MARJ] Isn't it obvious?
It has to be Valerie.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Wow, guys.
She's even livestreaming.
Excuse me.
You know, guys,
with Ms. CEO's recent issue,
I'm not surprised if some people
are angry with her.
I mean,
I just hope her company won't be affected
because I'll feel sorry for them.
[VALERIE COOS INSINCERELY]
But anyways, enough of this negativity.
That makes people uglier.
So now, it's time for my stress-reliever.
Miss, please start already.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Yes.
[FRUSTRATED WHINE]
See? She's really behind this!
Hold me back, hold me back!
- I swear!
- Relax, relax.
We're not yet sure of that.
Val isn't answering.
I'll try her condo.
No, no, no! Don't.
I know where she is.
This is in Greenbelt.
- [MARJ SQUEALS]
- Where's Billy?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[VALERIE] Guys, I had such
a big problem earlier.
While I was at the store earlier,
it was so hard to choose between
the pink or the yellow bag.
[VALERIE] So I ended up
getting both of them.
I'll show you them later,
and let me know if I got the right choice,
if I got both of them right, or…
I think I should've just got the pink one,
but I don't know, the yellow--
Okay, please stop recording
for just five minutes.
Oh, look!
It's the famous CEO.
Famous for all the wrong reasons.
We've been trying to call you,
but you weren't answering.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Did you have anything to do with
LoveList getting hacked?
As well as my account?
Oh, so I'm a hacker now.
Brilliant, wow.
Does this face look like a hacker to you?
[VALERIE] Sweetie,
the only thing I hack is my diet.
I'm not saying that
you hacked us yourself.
What I'm asking
is if you had anything to do with it.
Paid someone to do it.
Can't you see I'm busy?
The damage those hackers did
to my company is no joke.
So we'll investigate
and take legal action as needed.
Go!
Karma's a bitch, isn't it?
What, am I the only person with
a grudge against you?
Am I your only enemy?
Are you sure about that?
I heard someone spray-painted
"Bitch" on your car,
which is something that really suits you.
Will you accuse me of doing that too?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
As you can see,
I've moved on.
I mean, look.
I'm enjoying my time with retail therapy.
Or I was, until you ruined my day.
Now, you're making up stories.
That's why your ex-fiancé left you.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh well.
Like mother, like daughter.
Your father left her too, right?
- [VALERIE GROANS]
- [MAN, WOMAN] Ma'am! Ma'am!
[BILLY] You don't go there!
- Dude!
- [VALERIE GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VALERIE WAILING]
- Valerie, are you all right?
[VALERIE] This nose isn't cheap!
You're gonna pay for this!
[VALERIE CRYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] Do you think we can
track down the hacker?
[JORDAN] We're gonna
fix this. Trust me.
[PRECIOUS] We have a visitor.
[ABI] I saw what happened
with LoveList.
I'm just mad at people
who can't fight without hiding.
Oliver's Family Day will be
this Saturday, okay?
Don't forget about it.
[MAN] Just tell me if you want
to hack LoveList again.
I got his location!
I'm outside the troll's house.
You're going too far!
[MAN] Hey!
- I said give that to me!
- Get off me! Help!